A Guide to the Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association, Inc. records FA085
Rockefeller Archive Center
- DLMA, Inc., 1957-1995; 2; 78.875 Cubic Feet 214 document cases
  - Projects, 1957-1995; 2.3; 42.125 Cubic Feet 121 document cases
    - American Stock Exchange, 1977-1980 (Box 76, Folder 951)
      Includes oversized design drawing by The Eggers Group P.C., architects and planners of the proposed new building for the American Stock Exchange, 1978.
    - American Telephone and Telegraph Company (AT&T), 1984 (Box 76, Folder 952)
    - Archives, 1995-1998 (Box 76, Folder 953)
      Correspondence regarding the need to preserve the D-LMA records for their historical value.
    - Archives - Phyllis Barr, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 954)
    - A. Eric Arctander - Artist (Box 76, Folder 955)
    - Asbestos, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 956)
    - Assay Office, 1966-1968 (Box 76, Folder 957)
      Includes a photo map of the proposed American Stock Exchange site and other major projects.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 19.
    - Assessments & Re-Assessments (of Property), 1980 (Box 76, Folder 958)
    - Association for A Better New York, Inc., 1969-1979, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 959)
    - Auto Free New York, 1983-1991 (Box 76, Folder 960)
      Includes plan for "Open Edge," an open space waterfront park on the west side of Manhattan from Battery Park City to 59th Street.
    - Avenue Magazine, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 961)
    - Banca Commerciale Italiana, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 962)
    - Battery Park City, 1952, 1966-1967 (Box 77, Folder 963)
    - Battery Park City, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 964)
    - Battery Park City, January-May 1969 (Box 77, Folder 965)
    - Battery Park City, June-November 1969 (Box 77, Folder 966)
    - Battery Park City - Master Development Plan, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 967)
    - Battery Park City, 1970-1972 (Box 77, Folder 968)
    - Battery Park City, 1973 (Box 78, Folder 969)
    - Battery Park City, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 970)
    - Battery Park City, 1975 (Box 78, Folder 971)
    - Battery Park City, January-May 1976 (Box 78, Folder 972)
    - Battery Park City, June 1976 (Box 78, Folder 973)
    - Battery Park City, July-December 1976 (Box 78, Folder 974)
    - Battery Park City, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 975)
      Photos of renderings of the Battery Park City residential building removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 20.
    - Battery Park City, January-March 1978 (Box 79, Folder 976)
    - Battery Park City, April-July 1978 (Box 79, Folder 977)
    - Battery Park City, August-December 1978 (Box 79, Folder 978)
    - Battery Park City, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 979)
    - Battery Park City, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 980)
    - Battery Park City, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 981)
      Includes architectural drawing of 1979 Battery Park Master Plan with 1981 dates and revision.
    - Battery Park City, 1982-1983 (Box 80, Folder 982)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 21.
    - Battery Park City, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 983)
    - Battery Park City, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder 984)
      Photos of Battery Park City and proposed Styuvesant High School removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 22.
    - Battery Park City, 1988-1990 (Box 80, Folder 985)
    - Battery Park City - Peterson Plan (Re: Lower Manhattan Study), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 986)
    - Battery Park City - Publications - "Battery News", 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 987)
    - Battery Park City - Reports, 1976, 1977, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 988)
      See also Series 2.5, Boxes 208-209.
    - Battery Park City Parks Corporation, 1991-1994 (Box 81, Folder 989)
    - Battery Park Conservancy, 1993-1994 (Box 81, Folder 990)
    - Friends Of Battery Park - Roland Peracca, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 991)
    - Bicentennial, New York City, 1974-1975 (Box 82, Folder 992)
    - Bicentennial, New York City, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 993)
    - Bicentennial, New York City - Brochures, etc., 1974-1976 (Box 82, Folder 994)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 23.
    - 1987 Bicentennial of Constitution - New York City Commission, 1986-1987 (Box 83, Folder 995)
    - Bicentennial/1989 Activities, 1988-1989 (Box 83, Folder 996)
      George Washington's journey from Mt. Vernon to New York City in 1979. 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration, April 30, 1989.
      Photos from Centennial Celebration 1889 removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 24.
    - "Bike To Work Week," May 15-19, 1985 - Posters, 4 copies (Box 83, Folder 997)
    - Bond Transfer Tax, New York City (Bonds Tax Exempt), 1976, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 998)
      Tax Reform Bill of 1985, H.R. 3838
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), 1979-1982 (Box 83, Folder 999)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 1000)
      Includes a copy of the Certificate of Incorporation.
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) - "Waiting in the Wings," May 13, 1984, 1983-1988 (Box 83, Folder 1001)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), 1985-1988 (Box 84, Folder 1002)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), 1989-1990 (Box 84, Folder 1003)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC), 1991-1994 (Box 84, Folder 1004)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) - Triplex - Board of Directors and Planning Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 1005)
    - Bowling Green Park and Station Restoration, 1974, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 1006)
    - Bowling Green Park - Christmas Tree, 1983-1988, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 1007)
      Photos of 1986 Tree Lighting Ceremony removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 25.
    - Bowling Green Association/Art Piccolo Associates, 1985-1991 (Box 84, Folder 1008)
    - Bowling Green Park Association - Retirement Party Honoring Justin J. Murphy, May 4, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 1009)
    - Bowling Green Association, 1991-1994 (Box 85, Folder 1010)
    - Bridges (East River Restrictions), 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 1011)
    - Pedestrian Bridge Over Brooklyn Battery Tunnel Approach, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 1012)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Arches, 1974-1977 (Box 85, Folder 1013)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 85, Folder 1014)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Commission, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 1015)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Commission, January-April 1983 (Box 85, Folder 1016)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Commission, May December 1983 (Box 85, Folder 1017)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Commission, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 1018)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Film Project, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 1019)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Southeast, 1961-1970 (Box 86, Folder 1020)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Southwest, 1959-1960 (Box 86, Folder 1021)
      Includes architectural drawing.
    - Brooklyn Bridge Southwest, 1961-1963 (Box 86, Folder 1022)
      Includes architectural drawing - City of New York Housing and Redevelopment Board, Brooklyn Bridge Southwest, Urban Renewal Project, Lloyd B. Reid, traffic and engineering consultant, August 3, 1961.
    - Brooklyn Bridge Southwest, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 1023)
      Includes New York City Mayor Robert F. Wagner's press release of January 10, 1964 with photo of the planned development.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 26.
    - Brooklyn Bridge Southwest, 1965-1967 (Box 86, Folder 1024)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 27.
    - Buildings and Employment Capacity - New-Modernized, Bought-Sold-Rentals, 1970-1989 (Box 87, Folder 1025)
      Includes newspaper clippings. Handwritten on Folder: "Company Moves In & Out of New York City," 1970-1972.
    - Buildings and Employment Capacity - New-Modernized, Bought-Sold-Rentals, 1970-1989 (Box 87, Folder 1026)
      Includes newspaper clippings. Handwritten on Folder: "Company Moves In & Out of New York City," 1973-1975.
    - Buildings and Employment Capacity - New-Modernized, Bought-Sold-Rentals, 1970-1989 (Box 87, Folder 1027)
      Includes newspaper clippings. Handwritten on Folder: "Company Moves In & Out of New York City," 1977-1981.
    - Buildings and Employment Capacity - New-Modernized, Bought-Sold-Rentals, 1970-1989 (Box 87, Folder 1028)
      Includes newspaper clippings. Handwritten on Folder: "Company Moves In & Out of New York City," 1982-1990.
    - Bus - "Culture Loop", 1973-1975 (Box 87, Folder 1029)
    - Bus Loop, 1990-1993 (Box 87, Folder 1030)
    - Bus Loop, 1994-1995 (Box 88, Folder 1031)
      With several undated correspondence.
    - Bus Shelters, 1975, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 1032)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 28.
    - Business Council of New York State, 1982-1992 (Box 88, Folder 1033)
    - Business Labor Working Group, 1976-1978 (Box 88, Folder 1034)
    - Busker's Fare '94, June 28-July 4, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 1035)
      Presented by the Lower Manhattan Cultural Council (LMCC).
    - Cadwalader, Wickersham and Taft, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 1036)
      Barbara L. Christen's remarks at Bicentennial celebration, June 4, 1992.
    - Canopies on Broadway (Roy Rogers), 1984 (Box 88, Folder 1037)
    - Castle Clinton National Monument, 1975, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 1038)
    - Census, 1978, 1980, 1982, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 1039)
    - Central Business Development District - Administrative Code, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 1040)
    - Chambers - Canal Civic Association, 1971-1984 (Box 88, Folder 1041)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 29.
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1962-1988 (Box 89, Folder 1042)
      Images include: exteriors (1965), Chase Manhattan Bank Choral Group - Easter Concert on The Plaza, April 15, 1965 and demolition of the Mutual Life Insurance Company prior to the construction of the Chase Manhattan Bank building and plaza.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 30.
    - Child Care, 1990-1993 (Box 89, Folder 1043)
    - Citizen's Commission for Fire Protection in Lower Manhattan, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 1044)
    - The City Club of New York, 1981-1992 (Box 89, Folder 1045)
    - Civic Center (New York), 1964-1969 (Box 89, Folder 1046)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 31.
    - Civic Center Presentation, 1991-1992 (Box 89, Folder 1047)
    - Civic Executives Conference of Metropolitan New York, 1966, 1975-1985 (Box 89, Folder 1048)
    - Coalition for the Bight, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 1049)
    - Coast Guard Building, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 1050)
      Building is located between the Staten Island Ferry and Battery Park.
    - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 1051)
    - Commodities Exchanges (COMEX), 1989-1992 (Box 89, Folder 1052)
    - Commuter Bus Service from Grand Central Terminal to Lower Manhattan (and other Bus Services), 1973-1980 (Box 89, Folder 1053)
    - D-LMA Commuter Study - Grand Central Terminal to Lower Manhattan, February 1973 (Box 90, Folder 1054)
      Vollmer Associates, preliminary study.
    - Commuter Questionnaire Survey on Express Bus Service from Grand Central Terminal to Lower Manhattan, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 1055)
    - Commuter Van Service Policy Study, 1985-1986 (Box 90, Folder 1056)
      Transportation Division of the Department of City Planning.
    - Con Edison and Power Authority, 1974-1977 (Box 90, Folder 1057)
      Includes system blackout and restoration report for the system outage of July 13-14, 1977. Report dated July 26, 1977.
    - Con Edison and Power Authority, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 1058)
    - Con Edison and Power Authority, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 1059)
    - Con Edison and Power Authority, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 1060)
    - Con Edison and Power Authority, 1982-1983, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 1061)
    - Convention Center (Jacob K. Javits), 1977-1986 (Box 91, Folder 1062)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 32.
    - Convention Center - Comparison of Potential Sites, June 1977 (Box 91, Folder 1063)
      1. Battery Park City 2. 30th Street Railroad Yard 3. 44th Street
    - Convention Center - Photos (Box 91, Folder 1064)
      Potential Convention Center sites with views from Battery Park City (BPC), 33rd Street and 44th Street.
      Envelope of 35mm contact sheets removed. RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 33.
    - Convention Center - Press Kit, May 5, 1977; 2 portfolios (Box 91, Folder 1065)
      Each Kit has 1 photo and 3 site maps.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 1, Folder 34.
    - Coenties Slip - Coenties Slip Park Project, 1979-1984 (Box 91, Folder 1066)
    - Coenties Slip - Coenties Slip Park Project, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 1067)
    - Coenties Slip - Coenties Slip Park Project, 1986-1988 (Box 92, Folder 1068)
    - Coenties Slip - Coenties Slip Park Project, 1989-1994 (Box 92, Folder 1069)
    - Coenties Slip - Coenties Slip Park Project, 1989-1994 (Box 92, Folder 1069A)
    - Coenties Slip Park Project - Dissolution/Project and Financial Materials, 1981-1994 (Box 92, Folder 1070)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum of Design - "Immovable Objects" Exhibition in Lower Manhattan, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 1071)
    - Cooper Union, 1989-1990 (Box 93, Folder 1072)
    - Council for Urban Economic Development, 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 1073)
    - Council of Presidents, 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 1074)
    - Council of Presidents, 1986-1987 (Box 93, Folder 1075)
    - Council of Presidents, 1988-1990 (Box 93, Folder 1076)
    - Crime Statistics, 1972-1984 (Box 93, Folder 1077)
    - Custom House, 1970-1974 (Box 93, Folder 1078)
    - Custom House - Custom House Institute Planning Study, February 1, 1974 (Box 94, Folder 1079)
    - Custom House, 1975-1978 (Box 94, Folder 1080)
    - Custom House, 1979-1983 (Box 94, Folder 1081)
    - Custom House, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 1082)
    - Custom House, 1985-1986 (Box 94, Folder 1083)
    - Custom House, 1987-1990 (Box 95, Folder 1084)
    - Dematteis Organizations (DeM Builders), 1979-1993 (Box 95, Folder 1085)
    - Dey Street (Escalators), 1977-1979 (Box 95, Folder 1086)
      Includes map of businesses on Dey Street from Broadway to Church Street.
    - The Douglass Leigh Organizations, Inc., 1989-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1087)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 35.
    - Downtown Sites (Box 95, Folder 1088)
      A photo file of various sites: The Museum of the American Indian, Federal Courthouse building in Foley Square, etc.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 36.
    - Downtown Treasure (Hanover Square/Heritage Trail), 1994 (Box 95, Folder 1089)
    - Drugs, 1978, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 1090)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Letters Soliciting for Grant, 1965-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1091)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Agreement Forms for Member Grants (A-C), 1965-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1092)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Agreement Forms for Member Grants (D-L), 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 1093)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Agreement Forms for Member Grants (M-R), 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 1094)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Agreement Forms for Member Grants (S-Z), 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 1095)
    - East Side Subway Study (Traffic and Transportation) - Participating and Not Participating, 1965-1966 (Box 96, Folder 1096)
    - Education, 1982-1988 (Box 96, Folder 1097)
    - Education, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1098)
    - Education, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 1098A)
    - Education, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 1099)
    - Education, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 1100)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (Channel 13 WNDT), 1961-1964 (Box 97, Folder 1101)
    - Educational Broadcasting Corporation (Channel 13 WNDT) - "Another Day Downtown" TV Program, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 1102)
    - Edward S. Gordon Company, Inc. (ESG), 1983-1987 (Box 97, Folder 1103)
    - Ellis Island, 1963-1978 (Box 97, Folder 1104)
      Includes newspaper clippings and pamphlets, as well as correspondence. Photos and press packet from February 24, 1966 Groundbreaking Ceremony and Philip Johnson plan press conference.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 37.
    - Ellis Island, 1979-1983 (Box 98, Folder 1105)
    - Ellis Island, 1984-1993 (Box 98, Folder 1106)
      Four photos of layout of World Conference Center removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 38.
    - Ellis Island Bridge, 1993-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1107)
    - Employment, 1964-1990 (Box 98, Folder 1108)
    - Energy, 1977-1987 (Box 98, Folder 1109)
    - Energy - Energy Taxes - New York State, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 1110)
    - Environmental (Air, Noise, Pollution Control, etc.), 1971-1991 (Box 98, Folder 1111)
      Includes map - survey of the location of litter baskets in Lower Manhattan south of Chambers Street, 1974.
    - Evacuation Day Parade, November 26, 1983, 1983-1984 (Box 99, Folder 1112)
    - Exchange Alley, 1978-1983 (Box 99, Folder 1113)
    - Exchange Square, 1975-1977 (Box 99, Folder 1114)
    - Federal Emergency Management Administration (FEMA), 1994 (Box 99, Folder 1115)
    - Federal Hall National Memorial, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 1116)
      National Park Service, Walking Tour brochure.
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1976-1983 (Box 99, Folder 1117)
      Three construction photos of bank removed. See RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 39.
    - Ferry Service, 1986-1992 (Box 99, Folder 1118)
      Includes several copies of a pamphlet entitled "NYC Ferry Guide" by the New York City Department of Transportation.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 40.
    - Films - Die Hard 3, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 1119)
    - Films - Script for the Film "The Downtown Story", 1960-1962 (Box 99, Folder 1120)
      This film was prepared by the Chase Manhattan Bank to explain the urban renewal program undertaken for the downtown financial community, 1962.
    - Films - "The Downtown Story" - Film Showings and Receptions, 1960-1961 (Box 99, Folder 1121)
    - Films - Metro, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 1122)
    - First Precinct - Community Council (Police), 1975-1989 (Box 100, Folder 1123)
    - First Precinct - Community Council (Police), 1975-1989 (Box 100, Folder 1123A)
    - First Precinct - Community Council (Police), 1990-1994 (Box 100, Folder 1124)
    - First Winthrop Corporation - 61 Broadway - Fire Safety, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 1125)
      Leasing Office.
    - Fishport (Port Authority Fishport), 1984 (Box 100, Folder 1126)
    - Flag Day, 1980-1983 (Box 100, Folder 1127)
    - Flag Day, 1984-1986 (Box 100, Folder 1128)
    - Flag Day, 1987-1988 (Box 100, Folder 1129)
    - Flag Day, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 1130)
    - Flying Flags, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 1131)
      Wall Street. Flag Survey/Building Questionnaire
    - Fountains, 1976-1979 (Box 101, Folder 1132)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 41.
    - Fourth of July in Old New York - July 4, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 1133)
    - Fraunces Tavern, 1963-1990 (Box 101, Folder 1134)
      Includes an architectural drawing, annual reports, invitations to events such as the Washington's Birthday celebration, etc.
      See also Series 2.3, Boxes 111-113, Folders 1202-1212.
    - Fulton Street, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 1135)
      Contains correspondence, reports, newspaper clippings, widening, South Street Seaport Restoration, etc.
    - Fulton Street, 1959-July 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1136)
    - Fulton Street, August-December 1961 (Box 102, Folder 1137)
    - Fulton Street, 1962-1969 (Box 102, Folder 1138)
    - Fulton Street - Subway Station - Refurbishing, 1982 (Box 102, Folder 1139)
    - Fulton Street - Widening, 1958-1961 (Box 102, Folder 1140)
      Includes: "Notes on Fulton Street Widening" Skidmore, Owings and Merrill, Memo of August 29, 1958 "Traffic Study - Fulton Street," Edwin S. Voorhis and Son, Inc. (Prepared for the Fulton Street Association, March 10, 1959) D-LMA "Brief in Support of Fulton Street Widening," 1961
      Additional copies of D-LMA "Brief in Support of Fulton Street Widening," 1961 available in Series 2.5, Box 212, Folder 1888.
    - Galbreath Riverbank (Managing Agent for 61 Broadway) - Rent, Insurance, Electric and Other Payments, 1987-1994 (Box 102, Folder 1141)
      Original Managing Agent, 1987-1990 was Winthrop Properties.
    - Gateway American Committee, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 1142)
    - Global Economic Action Institute, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 1143)
    - Goldman Sachs (85 Broad Street Building), 1979-1980, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 1144)
    - Greenwich Street Development District, 1970-1984 (Box 102, Folder 1145)
    - Hamilton-Madison House, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1146)
      Barbara L. Christen was a Director of Hamilton Madison House and also Chair of the Membership Committee circa 1990.
    - Hamilton-Madison House, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 1147)
    - Hamilton-Madison House, 1992-1994 (Box 103, Folder 1148)
    - Hamilton-Madison House - Barbara L. Christen, 1989-1992 (Box 103, Folder 1149)
    - Hanover Square, 1975-1979 (Box 104, Folder 1150)
    - Harbor Festival, 1980-1989 (Box 104, Folder 1151)
    - Hearst Dinner - General, 1960-August 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1152)
      11th Annual Presentation of William Randolph Hearst Commemorative Gold Medals of Award - 1960 Achievement and 1960-1961 Special Award - sponsored by the DLMA to foster civic improvement. Program held October 10, 1961. Contains payment invoices, staff time sheets, planned seating charts and diagrams, invitations (acceptances and declinations), etc. for the event held at The Plaza Hotel on October 10, 1961.
    - Hearst Dinner - General, September-November 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1153)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 42.
    - Hearst Dinner - Dinner Committee, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 1154)
      11th Annual Presentation of William Randolph Hearst Commemorative Gold Medals of Award - 1960 Achievement and 1960-1961 Special Award - sponsored by the DLMA to foster civic improvement. Program held October 10, 1961.
    - Hearst Dinner - Free Tickets, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1155)
    - Hearst Dinner - Miscellaneous (Includes Newspaper Clippings), 1959-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1156)
    - Hearst Dinner - Orders Received, October 10, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1157)
    - Hearst Dinner - Photos, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1158)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 43.
    - Hearst Dinner - Printing, October 10, 1961, 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1159)
    - Hearst Dinner, October 10, 1961 - Regrets (Box 105, Folder 1160)
    - Hearst Dinner, May 15, 1962 - General (Box 105, Folder 1161)
    - Heart of the Arts, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 1162)
    - Heliport, 1971-1985 (Box 105, Folder 1163)
    - Heritage Trail (and Historic Sites), 1976-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1164)
    - Heritage Trail (and Historic Sites), 1994 (Box 106, Folder 1165)
    - The High School of Economics and Finance, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 1166)
    - Historic Districts, 1977, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 1167)
    - Historic Sites Committee, 1966-1967, 1991, 1993 (Box 106, Folder 1168)
      Photos and press packet from February 24, 1966 Groundbreaking Ceremony and Philip Johnson plan press conference.
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 44.
    - History (Downtown Manhattan), 1971-1991 (Box 106, Folder 1169)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 45.
    - Holocaust Museum, 1986-1990 (Box 106, Folder 1170)
      RAC Photograph Collection, Series 1081, Box 2, Folder 46.
    - Homeport (Staten Island, New York), 1984-1988 (Box 106, Folder 1171)
      U. S. Navy's proposed Surface Action Group Homeport in Stapleton, Staten Island, New York. Includes a Nuclear Homeport Danger Study and press releases of the Homeport Information Task Force, etc.